迪尔邦
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
苏·迪尔邦的失踪
The disappearance of Sue Dearbon.
我觉得我从没见过你对一个案子这么投入
I don't think I've ever seen you this devoted to a case.
我想成为一位为超能力者辩护的律师
I want to become a defense attorney for meta-humans.
来见见切斯特·P·朗克
Meet Chester P. Runk.
他不小心打开了一个黑洞
He opened a black hole by accident.
大家闹起来
What up, party people?
还有  我在哪里
Also where am I?
他的分子需要在亚原子水平上
His molecules need to re-stabilize
重新达到稳定
at the subatomic level.
等他出来了
And when he does get out,
他就知道自己想干什么了
that boy knows exactly what he wants to do.
约娜塔莉吗
Gonna ask Natalie out?
你无法避免眼前的危机
But you cannot avoid the coming crisis.
-告诉我怎么做  -闪电侠必须死
- Tell me what I can do. - The Flash must die.
纳什  如果你愿意告诉我们
Nash, if you could just tell us
你在那下面找什么
what you're looking for down there,
我们也许能帮你
we might be able to help you.
原来你一直藏在这里
So this is where you've been hiding.
我知道如何拯救巴里·艾伦
I know how to save Barry Allen.
这就是我拿手的
This is what I do.
我不仅仅解开谜团  我还揭露神话
I don't just solve mysteries, I bust myths.
将它们完全曝光
I bust them wide open.
你说你能救巴里
You said you could save Barry.
告诉我们你是什么意思  真相
Tell us what you meant. The truth.
你们知道自己面对的是什么吗
Do you know what you're dealing with?
那个监视者  马尔·诺武
The Monitor, Mar Novu,
或者无论他叫自己什么
or whatever we calls himself.
你是说监视者在这里吗
Are you saying the Monitor's here?
是的
That's right.
你追踪一个多元宇宙之神到了一个洞里
You tracked a Multiverse god down to a hole?
他将要在这里
And he's going to do here
做他在其他所有地球上都做过的事
what he has done on all these other Earths--
制造恐慌  因为监视者是个骗子
create fear because the Monitor is a fraud.
他是虚假的神
He's a false god.
我打算干掉他  这样就能救你的丈夫了
One that I intend to take down, thereby saving your husband.
如果我的计算正确
If my calculations are correct,
在这些石头后面有一个次元传送门
behind these rocks there's an inter-dimensional portal,
那个传送门会把我们直接引向马尔·诺武
and that portal will lead us directly to Mar Novu.
他一直都在这里
He's been here all along.
他无处可逃了
He has nowhere to run.
后退
Back up.
不  我不建议你这么做
Yeah, uh, no. I wouldn't do it...
巴里
Barry!
Barry.
你知道会发生这种情况吗
Did you know that would happen?
没错
Yeah.
这不过是马尔·诺武的又一个小伎俩
Look, this is just another one of Mar Novu's tricks.
这些石头中充满了恒金
These rocks are infused with Eternium, and that creates
这样形成了一个反震力场
an anti-vibrational force field that--
-无法穿越  -正确  无法穿越
- No phasing. - No phasing, correct.
那我们如何通过
So how do we get through?
我车里有把手提钻  那我
I've got a jackhammer in my car, so...
不
Uh, no.
与这些沉积物中的恒金产生任何接触
Any contact with the Eternium in this sediment
都可能引起灾难性的分子爆炸
could cause a catastrophic molecular blast.
大家都会死
Everybody dies.
实际上  我只需要一样物品
No instead, all I need is an artifact.
一样可以点亮恒金的东西
One that will illuminate the Eternium
那样我就能知道哪些石头可以挖掘
so I can know what rocks to dig around.
很简单  而且我知道上哪能找到这件物品
Simple, and I'd know where to find that artifact.
闪 电 侠
第六季
第六集
大家闹起来
What up, party people?
有人吗
Uh, hello?
大伙都去哪了
Where is everybody?
切斯特·P  切斯特·P  小伙子
Chester P. Chester P., my brother.
这个价值数十亿的尖端科技机构
You have a multi-billion dollar bleeding edge tech facility
都任由你使用了
all to yourself.
他什么都有
He has everything.
我来咯
Incoming!
声波扳手
A sonic wrench?
早上好  州长
Good morning, guv'nor!
我是神秘博士
I'm the Doctor!
他们还有一个多操控私人全球卫星监控系统
They have a multi-rigged private global satellite surveillance system?
该查查我的邮件了
Time to check my emails.
登录名
密码
账户失效
失效
Disabled?
我再试试  再试试
I'm going again. I'm going again.
切斯特·P·朗克
讣告
冰霜杀手
Killer Frost.
偏偏在我值班的时候
The one day I get watch duty.
这是什么意思
Uh, what does this mean?
严格意义上来说  你已经死了
Looks like technically you're dead.
我能碰吗
Can I touch it?
正式的伸缩人徽章
The official Elongated Man emblem.
他会兴奋地尖叫的  他会喜出望外
He's gonna scream. He's gonna be so surprised.
我一直在为整个团队筹备危机后的生活
I've been preparing the whole team for life after Crisis,
但是中城同样也需要
but Central City also has to be ready
准备好面对一个没有闪电侠的世界
for a world without Flash,
当我走了以后  伸缩人应该成为中城
and Elongated Man should be its sole protector
唯一的保护者
once I'm gone.
拉尔夫只以为  他明天会来中城警局
As far as Ralph knows, he's coming to CCPD
参加一次常规的取证
for a routine deposition tomorrow,
而实际上会是一场传递使命的新闻发布会
when it's really a press conference to pass the torch.
大伙
Hey guys.
收到你的信息了  乔
Got your message, Joe.
拉尔夫  我跟一个老朋友聊了下
Hey Ralph, I talked to an old friend
你的迪尔邦案子
about your Dearbon case.
我拿到了你在米德韦市寻找的地址
I got the address you were looking for in Midway City.
我如果是你  在明天的取证之后
If I were you, I would go check it out
就会去查查看
after the deposition tomorrow.
今天能去  为何推到明天  对吧
Why put off tomorrow what you can do it today, right?
-谢了  -等等
- Thanks. - Wait, wait, wait.
你明天早上可以从
Um, you're gonna be back from Midway
米德韦市回来吧
by tomorrow morning, right?
只是例行出庭作证  你可以的
It's a routine deposition. You can handle it.
我跟你一起去吧
Why don't I tag along?
我可以加快进度
I'll speed things up a bit.
你想帮我查案吗
You wanna help me with a PI case?
是的  会很好玩的
Yeah, definitely. It'll be fun.
我听你指挥
I'll follow your lead.
好
Okay.
看来要花点时间了
This looks like it's gonna take awhile.
如果你知道怎么打好关系就不一样了
Not if you know how to work the system.
我整个夏天都在参加有钱人
I spent the whole summer hobnobbing
名人和恶人的饭局
with the rich, famous, and the infamous.
放轻松  交给我
Relax, I got this.
难以相信整个夏天
Yeah, I can't imagine spending a whole summer
都在这群人中做卧底
undercover with this crowd.
盛装晚宴
What does a gala event
和苏的失踪有什么关系
have to do with Sue's disappearance anyway?
就在苏消失之前  有人看到她
Right before Sue vanished, she was seen wearing
在米兰穿着独一无二的维多利亚婚纱
a one-of-a-kind Victoria Veil dress in Milan.
这张照片是三周前拍的
This photo was taken three weeks ago.
一模一样的婚纱
It's the exact same dress.
苏来过这里
Sue was here.
要么她还在这
And either she's still here
要么里面的人知道她为什么不在
or somebody in there knows why she isn't.
该着装了
Time to suit up.
摘下戒指  朋友
Lose the ring, pal.
这才是我们今晚的着装
This is how we suit up tonight.
要说这里有谁知道苏的下落
So if anyone here knows where Sue is,
非派对主人莫属
it'll be the party's host.
这里面有上百号人
There's hundreds of people in here.
我们要怎么缩小范围
How do we narrow it down?
-请出示金砖  先生  -谢谢
- Golden tile, sir. - Thank you.
贵宾室
The VIP lounge.
那是所有人
That's where anyone who's anyone
趋炎附势的地方
will be going to kiss the proverbial ring.
我们要进去
We need to get in there.
来  我的领结也紧了  我帮你
Here, mine was tight too. Just let me...
这下我拍了巴里·艾伦的十张鼻孔照
Now I have ten selfies of inside Barry Allen's nose.
拍照领结
A camera tie?
怎么  你也有藏刀鞋和抓钩皮带吗
What, you have a knife shoe and a grapple-hook belt too?
也许吧
Maybe.
施展魅力的时候到了  等我信号
Time to charm. Wait for my signal.
拉尔夫  信号是...
Ralph, what's the...
我还以为今晚最美的
And here I thought the paintings would be
会是油画
the most beautiful thing tonight.
我错了
I was wrong.
拉尔夫·德比
Ralph Dibny.
詹纽瑞·加罗尔
January Galore.
我没在这种晚宴上见到过你
I haven't seen you at one of these events before.
那是因为我去年都在我迪拜的岛上
That's because I spent the last year on my island in Dubai.
我和我合伙人把公司卖了
My partner and I sold our corporation.
巴里
Barry?
杜松子马天尼  酒壶摇的  不要搅拌的
GinGold martini. Shaken, not stirred.
恭喜你把公司卖了  巴里
Congratulations on selling your corporation, Barry.
我真心希望你把赚到利润
I do hope you reinvested your profits
再投资到抵押贷款上
in collateralized loan obligations.
是的  最近我们把公司卖了
Yes, we recently sold our company
赚了几百万美金
for many millions of dollars.
你认识晚宴的主人吗
Do you know our host?
-迈耶斯先生吗  -对  迈耶斯先生
- Mr. Meyers? - Yes, Mr. Meyers.
今天晚宴的主人是雷明顿·迈斯特
The host of this event is Remington Meister.
你们是来晚宴捣乱的吧
You both crashed this event, didn't you?
想要一些免费的建议吗
Would you like some free advice?
要是我就在可怕的人找上门之前就闪人
I'd leave before someone scary comes and finds you.
搭讪不怎么顺利
Well, that did not go well.
非也
Yes, it did.
我们的贵宾门票
Our VIP ticket.
策略
Finesse.
哈里森·威尔斯
Harrison Wells?
你是谁
Okay, who are you?
-阿莱格拉  -你是那个实习生
- Allegra. - You're the intern.
也许你能帮我个忙
So maybe you can help me with something.
我在找紫外线发射器
I'm looking for a UV emitter,
但是我的扫描仪显示
and my scanner tells me
紫外线发射器就在这里
there is a UV emitter right around here.
你不是死了吗
You're supposed to be dead.
怎么回事  你假死吗
What happened? Did you fake your own death?
什么  没有
What? Oh, no.
所以  你以为我是哈里森·威尔斯
So you, uh, no. You think I'm Harrison Wells.
我不是哈里森·威尔斯
I'm not Harrison Wells.
我叫纳什  纳什·威尔斯
My name is Nash. Nash Wells.
你和他长得一模一样
You look just like him.
是的  二重身的确长得一模一样
Yeah, well, doppelgangers are like that.
愚蠢的地球
Stupid Earth.
-好吧  阿赛伦  - 我叫阿莱格拉
- Okay, Accelerant. - Allegra.
我在做一项调查
I'm doing a dig, all right?
我需要紫外线来完成我的调查
I need UV rays to complete my dig.
你  根据我的护手显示
You, according to my gauntlet...
是一个有紫外线的超能力者
Are a meta-human with UV capabilities.
明白我的意思了吗
You see where I'm going here?
你要我用我的超能力来帮你
You want me to use my powers to help you?
-没错  -我帮不了你
- Yes! - I can't help you.
什么  为什么
What? Why not?
那不重要  答案是帮不了
Never mind. The answer is no.
阿莱格拉  我和你做个交易吧
Allegra, I will make you a deal.
你用紫外线...
You help me with the--
来帮我
UV thing,
我就告诉你本世纪的独家新闻
and I will give you the scoop of the century.
二重身  多重宇宙  以及我们知道的
Doppelgangers, Multiverse, and potentially
所有生命潜在的终点
the end of all life as we know it.
听起来怎么样
Now how does that sound to you?
告诉更多关于多重宇宙的事
Tell me more about this Multiverse.
银行解除冻结你的账户了
The bank unfroze your accounts,
也许我帮你恢复驾照时
and maybe I erased your parking tickets
把你的停车罚单给删了
when I got your driver's license reinstated.
谢了  塞西尔
Thanks, Cecile!
你的客户能有你真幸运
Oh, your clients are lucky to have you.
对了  说到这个
Hey, speaking of,
我应该让你回去工作了
I should let you get back to doing your job.
非常感谢
Thank you so much
你所做出的一切
for everything that you've done.
等下  你等一下  切斯特
Wait, you know what? Hey, Chester.
我还有些时间
I got--I got a little time.
有没有什么其他地方
Is there--is there anything else
你还需要帮忙的
that you could use some help with.
没了  切斯特这边一切都好
Hmm, nope. All is good in Chester-hood.
等下
Wait!
别走  别走
Don't go! Don't go!
你确定吗  你真的确定吗
Are you sure? Like are you sure-sure?
真没有什么我能帮你的了吗
Anything at all that I could help you with?
我是说  使劲想想
I mean, think hard.
是有些事情
There is something.
我就知道  好了  交给我吧
I knew it! Okay, sock it to me.
吉特斯没了  对吗
Jitters is gone, right?
也就是说我再也见不到娜...
Which means that I'll never see Na...
他们的咖啡了
their coffee again.
是  我想你说的咖啡是指娜塔莉吧
Yeah, I'm thinking that by coffee, you mean Natalie?
我正想要约她出去
I was gonna ask her out
在我打满震波奇诺集点卡之后
after I filled out my Vibe-acino punch card.
但是现在太晚了  所以...
But it's too late now, so...
对不起  我知道这不是律师的问题
Sorry, I--I know this isn't a lawyer problem at all.
不  不是
No, it's not,
但这是共情超能力的问题
but it is a meta-empath problem.
你有  你有能力
You got--you got powers?
我有能力
Oh, I have powers.
那真是太酷了
Oh, that's so cool!
真是太酷了
That's so cool!
那作为检察官这里肯定有些
That must've been a major conflict of interest
重大利益冲突吧
as a DA though.
没错  是的
It was. Yeah.
但这些能力将会帮你约娜塔莉出来
Uh, but those powers are about to help you ask out Natalie.
-好  -咱们开始吧
- Yeah! - Let's do it.
-好  -好  我们决定了
- Yeah! - Okay, we're doing it.
我的客人很少有足够的勇气
Very few of my guests have the tapferkeit
这样直接挑战我
to challenge me like this.
毕竟  我是这个场子的主人
After all, I'm the master of this ring.
专业麻将规则
Strict rules of Mahjong?
当然了
But of course.
好了  先生们
Oh, so gentlemen,
我们想我们还没有互相介绍过
I don't think we have been introduced.
我是雷明顿·迈斯特  今天的主人
I'm Remington Meister, your host.
那你们呢
And you are?
我名叫德比  拉尔夫·德比
The name's Dibny. Ralph Dibny.
艾伦  巴里...
Allen. Barry--
很高兴认识你们  艾伦·巴里和拉尔夫·德比
Well, nice to meet you, Allen Barry and Ralph Dibny.
是什么让你们来到了我这大派对的
Hmm, and what brings you to my wonderful grosse feier?
苏·迪尔邦
Sue Dearbon.
苏
Sue?
一个  非常聪明的年轻女人
A, uh, fiercely intelligent young woman.
她是你们的朋友吗
She's a friend of yours?
我是她的崇拜者
I'm an admirer of hers.
你很有品位  德比先生
Ah, you have taste, Mr. Dibny.
我希望我能做个更好的主人
And I wish I could be a more auspicious host
来介绍你们认识
and introduce you,
但是很遗憾迪尔邦女士不在这里
but I'm afraid Ms. Dearbon isn't here.
实际上  我从没看到她出现在任何社交场合
In fact, I don't think I've seen her at any social event
有六个多月的时间了
in over six months.
或许她会出现在你们那里的晚宴上
Perhaps she'll attend an event in your facility soon.
那么  你们是哪里来着
And, uh, where was that? What?
-巴黎  -迪拜
- Paris. - Dubai.
我们运作着一个多城市进出口公司
We run a multi-city import/export company.
或许她还在客人名单上
Maybe she's still on the guest list.
你知道  以防万一
You know, just in case.
你觉得我应该去查一下吗
You think I should check?
行啊
Sure, yeah.
英娜
Idna!
这裙子真漂亮
That's a beautiful dress.
是独一无二的吗
Is this one-of-a-kind?
其实是独一有二的
Two-of-a-kind, actually.
即使最固执的设计师作品也有能买到的价格
Even the most stubborn designer's one-of-a-kind outfit has a price.
真对
So true!
让我刮目相看啊
I'm impressed.
你对时尚很有眼光
You have quite the eye for fashion.
苏·迪尔邦不在名单上
Sue Dearbon is not on the list.
奇怪的是
And strange...
你们也不在
neither are you.
当一个像你这样的拍卖出现时
Well, when an auction like yours pops up,
没有名单能阻挡我们
no list can keep us away.
我喜欢你
I like you.
他  不怎么样
Him? Nicht so viel.
麻将
Mahjong.
看  我赢了
Sieg. I win.
能认识你们真是太好了
Such a pleasure to meet you both.
享受你们的夜晚吧
Enjoy the rest of your evening.
抱歉老兄  我以为我能处理
I'm sorry, man. I thought I had that.
我们应该回中城去了
I--we should get back to Central City.
让我们的朋友提高警惕
Put our friend above on high alert.
我找出了那个
I tracked down the woman
在米兰给苏设计衣服的女人
who designed Sue's dress in the Milan.
-是吗  -结果发现英娜
- Yeah. - It turns out that Idna
确实要求她又做了一套
did commission her to make another one.
所以我想下一步我们应该...
So I think what we gotta do next is probably--
拉尔夫  苏不在这里
Ralph, Sue's not here.
我们暴露了  还碰上了死胡同
We just got made and we just hit a dead end.
我们应该回中城去
We should head back to Central City.
巴里  如果迈斯特想让我们离开这里
Barry, if Meister wanted us out of here,
我们早就出去了
we'd be gone already.
好好闻闻  行吗
Take a whiff, would ya?
这里味道有什么不太对
Something doesn't smell right here.
拉尔夫  我知道你对苏的案子很上心
Ralph, I know you care about this Sue case,
但我们这是在勉强支撑
but we're grasping at straws.
我都不确定这里有谜团
I'm not even sure there's a mystery here.
真的吗  你不确定
Really? You're not sure?
看到那边戴眼罩的那个家伙了吗
You see that guy with the eye patch right there?
那是里格斯·惠灵顿
That's Riggs Wellington.
他是个阴暗的俄罗斯黑手党
he's a shady Bratva counterfeiter.
詹纽瑞·加罗尔
And January Galore?
她是地下的武器贩子
She's an underground weapons dealer.
那边的那位  是个毒品团伙头头
That guy right there, he's a drug kingpin.
和他说话的那个女人是个黑帮老大
The woman he's talking to is a mob boss.
如果这是罪犯狂欢夜
If this is a party for criminals,
那闪电侠和伸缩人
then the Flash and Elongated Man
就得出手管管了
need to take over.
别那么激动  可以吗
Pump the brakes, would ya?
面具和头罩需要在特定地点和时间使用
There's a time and a place for masks and cowls,
但不是现在
but this is not it.
这个迈斯特  他在密谋着什么
This Meister, he's up to something.
我们得找出来  无论要花多久
We need to find out what it is, no matter how long it takes.
拉尔夫  明天我们有取证要做...
Ralph, tomorrow we have-- we have the deposition--
先别管取证的事  可以吗
Lay off the whole deposition thing, would ya?
中城警局可以等
CCPD can wait.
我可以瞬间就把整个地方查个底朝天
I can search this whole place in seconds.
巴里  我知道你想帮忙
Barry, I realize that you want to help
我感谢你的好心  但这里不是中城
and I appreciate that, but this is not Central City,
这些人也不是超能力者
these people are not metas.
现在得用我们的人类身份
This is a time for our human identities.
用策略  记得吗
Finesse, remember?
-我需要点时间  好吗  -好的
- I just need some time, okay? - Okay.
计划是这样的
Here's the deal.
我用新的吉特斯点单服务点了一杯咖啡
I made a coffee order with the new Jitters-To-Go service.
那是娜塔莉现在工作的地方
That's where Natalie works now.
然后等她过来的时候
So when she arrives,
我去读她的情绪
I am going to read her emotion,
接着我来告诉你该说什么
and then I'm gonna tell you what to say.
-要是她拒绝我怎么办  -她不会拒绝的
- What if she says no? - She's not gonna say no!
有我的帮忙  不会的
Not with my help.
而且我也在这
And I'm here too.
我今天的日行一善就是助人为乐
My good deed for the day was to help somebody,
但我看谁都不顺眼
and I couldn't find anyone less annoying.
真的假的
Really?
我有一份给切斯特·P·朗克的外卖
Hey, I have a delivery for Chester P. Runk?
对的  那是...那是...那是我的
Yep, that's--that's-- that's, uh, that's me.
没错
Yeah.
12杯咖啡
Wow. 12 Vibe-acinos.
没错
Yeah.
切斯特  她很佩服你
Chester, she's feeling impressed.
这么大的一单
A big order like that,
这向她表明你是个大人物
it shows her that you are a man with means.
是啊  你知道的  我...
Yeah, well, you know, I'm a--
花钱就是这么大手大脚
kind of a big spender, you know?
这东西控制不住的  对吧
Can't take it with you, right?
我想是的吧
Sure. I guess.
你需要发票吗
Do you need a receipt?
你确定你读对了吗
Are you sure you're reading her right?
当然没错了
Yeah! Of course.
切斯特  她急需认可
Um, um, hey Chester, she's yearning for validation.
所以多夸夸她
So pay her a compliment.
她特别喜欢她的鞋子
She's feeling very strong, positive feelings about her shoes.
我
Uh, I--man.
我真的很喜欢你的这双鞋
I really like your shoes.
这双破鞋  不是吧
These old things? Yuck.
我最喜欢的那双不知道扔哪去了
I lost my favorite kicks to a black hole.
那挺让人难受的
That's, uh, that's rough.
你完全理解错了
You are totally missing the mark.
你一点忙都没在帮
You're not helping!
切斯特  肯定点  自信点
Uh, Chester, be assertive.
没开口约她  就别让她走
Don't let her leave without asking her out.
娜塔丽
Uh, Natalie.
你离开之前
Uh, before you go,
我在想...我们可不可以
I was wondering if-- if we could, you know,
我能不能帮你拿这个箱子
I--I could carry this crate for you.
-我自己能搞定  -她不能
- Oh, it's not a problem. - Yes, it is.
她需要你表现的体贴一点
She wants you to be chivalrous.
现在就帮她
Help her now!
姐妹  我明白
Girl, I got it.
对不起
Pardon moi?
我可以帮忙买下这些的
I could pay for this.
我觉得你已经够帮忙的了
Yeah, I think you've done enough.
我不是情感专家
I'm no expert,
《拉尔夫之书》
但《拉尔夫之书》说你想要约人出去的话
but the Book of Ralph says that when you ask someone out,
做自己就好了
you should just be yourself.
他这个样子要怎么做自己
How is he supposed to be himself
他都不知道自己是谁了
when he doesn't even know who he is anymore?
这些不同的地球
And these different Earths
同时存在  自从...
have existed simultaneously since...
自从...远古时代起
Well, since, uh--let's see. Oh, the dawn of time.
怎么会没人知道这个
Well, how come nobody knows about this?
这么大的一个东西
I mean, stuff this big?
应该警示公众的
The public should be made aware.
有人知道  该知道的人知道
People know. Just the right people.
普通大众  不会的
The general public? No, no.
那样不行  他们会疯的
No, that would not be good. They would lose their minds.
也对  我是说...
Right, I mean...
所有的都如此...
it's all so...
-壮丽  -是  很壮丽
- Epic. - Yes, it's epic.
二重身  反物质事件
Doppelgangers, anti-matter events,
极速者玩些双重身份
and speedsters juggling dual identities,
比如闪电侠和巴里·艾伦
like the Flash and Barry Allen.
等下  你说什么
Wait, what?
什么
What?
我老板的丈夫是闪电侠
My boss' husband is the Flash?
-大家什么都不告诉我  -但  当然了
- Ah, nobody tells me anything. - But then, of course,
我们也别忘了故事里的反派...
let's not forget the villain of this story--
监视者
the Monitor.
患有妄想症的大骗子
The cosmic imposter with delusions of grandeur.
因此我要干掉那个骗子  让他不得翻身
That is why I'm gonna take that fraud down permanently.
你要杀掉监视者吗
You're gonna kill this Novu guy?
故事就讲到这里
Enough story time.
是时候兑现你的承诺了
Time for you to hold up your end of the bargain.
等等  你可以解释一下二重身吗
Wait, can you explain doppelgangers?
当然  我可以  但首先
Sure, absolutely. I can, but first--
你先用超能力紫外线照一下这里
Let's have you zap this with your meta UV lights,
让我知道开挖时要避开哪些石头
so I can find out what rocks to avoid when I excavate.
开始吧
And go.
我
I...
我  我做不到
I-- I can't.
你能做到
Yes, you can.
你是一个超能力者  这就是真正的你
You're a meta. It's who you are.
不  我不是
No, it-- it's not.
你是  而且我们已经说好了
It is, and also we had a deal.
-交易取消  -什么
- Well, the deal's off. - What?
我不会成为你用来伤人的武器
I'm not gonna be some weapon you use to hurt others.
我没有让你变成武器
I'm not asking you to be the weapon.
我不是这样的人
It's not who I am.
好了  看看这里有什么
All right, let's see what we got here.
火环模拟
我感觉这应该不是约翰尼·卡什的歌
Something tells me that ain't a Johnny Cash song.
该死  拉尔夫  她不在这里
Damn it, Ralph. She's not here.
火环
他们来这里是为了竞拍这个
They're all here to bid on this.
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
传输完成
超能力者目标已获取
Meta target acquired.
太好了
Wunderbar.
别白费劲了  这上面有超能力抑制器
Don't bother. It's meta-dampened.
不得不说  我没想到中城的
I must say, I did not expect Central City's
常驻超级英雄在我的小聚会上不请自来
resident superhero to crash my little gathering.
不得不说
And I must say,
我没想到居然是这出邦德反派俗套戏码
I'm surprised by all the Bond villain clichés.
你有那种反派的口音  邪恶的阴谋
I mean, you've got the accent, the diabolical scheme,
甚至还有沉默但致命的追随者
even the silent but deadly henchperson.
致命紫光
Ultraviolet?
我把你关进了铁山监狱
I sent you to Iron Heights.
幸运的是  她在下面也有朋友
Luckily, she has friends in low places.
让我猜猜看
And let me guess,
你想把我的真身加入你的拍卖
you're gonna add my unmasking to your little auction?
我一点也不关心你的秘密身份  闪电侠
Oh, I could care less about your secret identity, Flash.
我的兴趣是全球性的
My interests are global.
现在想想  德比先生
And to think, Mr. Dibny,
是闪电侠触发了我的超能力活动监视器
that it was the Flash that set off my meta-activity monitor
然后触发了让你们被抓到的
that then triggered the security protocols
安全程序
that got you caught.
非常感谢
Danke schon.
但是我很好奇
I am very curious, though,
你们来这里的真正目的是什么
as to why you are really here.
你想要我告诉你吗
Do you expect me to talk?
不  德比先生
No, Mr. Dibny...
我想要你死
I expect you to die.
拜托
Oh, come on.
这是《金手指》里的台词
That line is literally from "Goldfinger."
这个也是
And so is this.
看好了
Behold,
一个目前最先进的工业激光炮
a state-of-the-art industrial laser cannon.
它会发射致命激光  就这样
It will shoot a deadly beam-- zap!--
穿透你们俩
through the both of you
就在中城被摧毁的瞬间
the moment Central City is destroyed.
中城
你打算杀死成千上万无辜的人
You're gonna kill millions of innocent people
就为了卖出你的武器吗
just to sell your weapon?
没错
Yeah.
好好欣赏吧
Enjoy the show.
中城
迷路了吧
Got lost, didn't you?
什么  没有
What? No.
-没有吗  -也许吧
- No? - Maybe.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我吓到你了  对吗
I freaked you out, didn't I?
在铁山监狱看布娃娃吃东西才叫恐怖
Watching Rag Doll eat while in Iron Heights is freaky.
当然  为什么要玩消失
Sure it is. So why the disappearing act?
事实上  让我猜一下
Actually, let me pause at theory on that.
我认为你害怕使用自己的超能力
I think you're afraid to use your powers
因为如果你用了
because if you do,
你认为自己就会变成某个人
you think you'll become like someone.
某个人
Someone.
是某个你认识的人  某个...
Someone you know, someone you...
你恨的人
hate.
我猜的对吗
How am I doing?
我表姐  伊丝丽兰萨  她能力和我一样
My cousin, Esperanza, she has the same powers as me,
但是她利用超能力杀人
only she uses them to murder people.
你不是你的表姐
You're not your cousin.
但是如果我开始使用超能力
But if I start using my powers,
有什么能阻止我变成她那样的人
what's to stop me from becoming like her?
因为我们选择自己的人生  阿莱格拉
Because, Allegra, in this life we choose.
我们选择成为什么样的人
We choose who we are.
如果你选择使用自己的超能力
So if you choose to use your incredible powers,
这不会让你变成伊丝丽兰萨
that does not make you anything like Esperanza
除非你做出和她一样的选择
unless you choose that.
-我不是伊丝丽兰萨  -你是谁
- I'm not Esperanza. - Who are you?
我是阿莱格拉
I'm Allegra.
是的
Yes.
阿莱格拉·加西娅
Allegra Garcia.
没错
Yes.
这可有点让人失望
Well, that was anti-climatic.
我成功了吗
Did I do it?
是的
Yes.
我想你成功了
I think you did.
你还好吗
How you holding up?
就像是奥德兰行星上最糟糕的一天
Hmm, like Alderaan on a bad day.
《星球大战》中被死星炸毁的星球
你的心情看起来也像是被炸毁了
You look pretty emotionally vaporized too.
切斯特  我想我是在用你的问题
Okay, Chester, I-- I think that I was using your problems
来分散我自己的情绪
as a distraction from my own feelings,
我内心的指南针已经彻底失灵了
and my internal compass was completely off,
所以我才会把娜塔莉的感觉理解为
and that made me sense the opposite
完全相反的意思
of what Natalie was feeling.
我很抱歉  非常非常抱歉
And I'm so sorry. I'm so, so sorry.
我已经拥有这些能力两年了
I've had these powers for two years now,
却还没搞清楚要怎么用
and I'm still figuring them out.
你现在感觉如何
How you feeling now?
说真的  我也说不好
Oh, uh, honestly, I don't know.
那就假装我是那个有共情能力的人
Let's pretend I'm the empath.
你会阻止什么样的感觉
What kind of feelings would you be putting off?
好  别这样  看着我的眼睛
Now, no. Stare into my eyes.
好
Okay.
想象我的瞳孔在转
And imagine my pupils are swirling.
转啊  转啊
And--and swirling, and swirling.
好了  亲爱的  那是催眠  不是共情
Okay, honey, that's a hypnotist, not an empath,
但我真的很感谢你的努力
but I really appreciate the effort.
-对  -没错  你说得对
- Yeah, uh... - Yeah, you're right.
我感觉如何  我...
How am I feeling? I'm...
天哪  我吓坏了
oh, my God. I'm freaking out.
你知道  我干了20年地检官
You know, I was a DA for 20 years,
然后他们一夜之间就把我换了
and they just--boom, replaced me overnight.
现在  我已经不知道我是谁了
And now I feel like I don't exactly know who I am anymore,
如果我做超能力者律师也失败了
and if I fail at this meta-attorney thing,
我就回不去了
I can't go back.
对  但你没有让我失望
Yeah, but you didn't fail me.
我觉得我们俩只需要相信
You know, I think the two of us just need to
真实的我们
trust that the real us
总会发光的
will always shine through.
所以我要拥抱新的自我
Which is why I will embrace the new me
去约娜塔莉出来约会
by finally asking out Natalie.
你知道  抓住当下之类的
You know, seize the moment and all that.
是啊
Yeah.
也许你也应该试试
And maybe you should too.
-对  -对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
也许我也应该试试
Maybe I should too.
我应该听你的话
I should've listened to you.
如果我们照你说的做  就不会被抓
If we'd done things your way, we wouldn't have gotten caught.
也许我应该把中城交给
Maybe I should be handing Central City
拉尔夫·德比而不是伸缩人
over to Ralph Dibny rather than Elongated Man.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
还没有正式宣布
There's no deposition.
我计划开个新闻发布会把你作为
I planned a press conference to
中城的官方保护者介绍给大家
present you as Central City's official protector.
因为即将到来的危机  我必须让这个城市
Because of this coming Crisis, I have to prepare
准备好迎接没有闪电侠的世界
the city for a world without Flash.
我...  我深感荣幸
I'm, uh...I'm honored
你觉得我可以成为你的继任者
that you think that I could help fill your shoes.
听着  今晚的工作是拉尔夫·德比的
Look, tonight's job was for Ralph Dibny
因为我身份的两个部分都是有价值的
because both parts of my identity have value.
你也一样
The same is true for you,
只有今晚  我可以利用你平民的身份
only tonight I could've used your civilian half.
我想说的是巴里·艾伦
What I'm trying to say is Barry Allen
跟闪电侠一样重要
is just as important as the Flash.
记住这句话
Try to remember that.
我知道我会记住
I know I will.
你能够到我的袖扣吗
You know, can you reach my cufflink?
-什么  -把我的袖扣拿下来
- What? - Grab my cufflink.
好  够到了
Yeah. Got it.
好  拿到了
All right, I got it.
好  我数三下
Okay, on three,
我想让你把它弹到那个激光炮里
I want you to flick it at that laser cannon.
一  二  弹
One, two, flick!
好了  成功了  它完蛋了
All right, I got it. It's down.
小心  这是怎么回事
Whoa, watch out. What was that?
好  我们怎么办
Okay, uh, what do we do?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们怎么办
Uh, what do we do?
天啊
Jeez!
我们怎样才能阻止它
How do we stop that?
-它是有规律的  -是吗
- There's a pattern. - Really?
好  我一说"现在"
All right, when I say now...
我们就往左边挪
fling ourselves to the left.
-好[右边]  -是左边
- Right. - The left!
现在
Now!
我们必须阻止迈斯特
We have to stop Meister.
他有致命紫光的保护
He's got Ultraviolet protecting him.
她的超能力可以杀了我们两个
Her powers could kill us both.
那我们用你的方法
Then let's do things your way,
来点小策略
with a little finesse.
是时候换装了
Time to suit up.
晚上好  我的朋友们
Good evening, meine freunde.
你们等待已久的时刻就要到来了
The moment that you've all been waiting for is here.
拍卖会现在开始
Let the auction begin.
火环
EYE-3C9卫星系统
The EYE-3C9 satellite system,
或者我更喜欢称它为火环
or as I'd like to call it the Ring of Fire,
它装备了15枚折光远程导弹
is equipped with 15 dioptric long-range missiles.
只要使用这个控制台
Simply use this console
输入我们想打击的位置坐标
to enter our desired coordinates,
然后就可以坐等
and then sit back
看着地狱之火降临到你敌人的头上
and watch hellfire reign down on your enemies.
我们现在做个小小的演示  好吗
Perhaps a little demonstration now, yes?
中城
这里不是卫生间吗
This isn't the bathroom?
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
艾伦·巴里先生  看来你找到了免费酒吧
Mr. Allen Barry, I see you have found the open bar.
在我靠近那个控制台之前吸引他的注意力
Keep her busy till I get to that console.
我也要竞拍你那个白痴笔记本电脑
I'll bid on your stupid laptop.
五亿
$500 million.
五亿零一美元
$500 million and one dollar.
"价高者得"原则
"Price is Right" rules.
致命紫光  礼貌地护送巴里先生出去
Ultraviolet, uh, gently escort Mr. Barry out,
但别把他的钱烧了
but don't burn his money.
我喜欢《真人快打》
I love "Mortal Kombat"!
德比先生  我们又见面了
Mr. Dibny, we meet again.
求你少说点邦德电影的台词  老兄
You've got to take it easy on the Bond quotes, man.
你知道我最喜欢哪部分吗
You know what my favorite part is?
"终结他"
"Finish him!"
通常我让致命紫光去杀人
You know, usually I allow Ultraviolet to do the killing.
但是对你  我会另行对待
But for you, I'll make an exception.
来吧
Come on!
炸药倒计时
Fire in the hole.
谢谢你的来访
Thanks for dropping in.
认真的吗  调整你的领结
Really? Adjusting your tie?
是调整闪光灯
Adjusting the flash.
启动自毁
老兄  做得好
Nice job, man.
难以置信
Shocking.
你的表现
Your performance...
巴里先生  棒极了
Wunderbar, Mr. Barry.
名字是艾伦
The name's Allen.
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
雷明顿·迈斯特的犯罪集团被端了
Remington Meister's crime ring is over.
能抓到雷明顿真好
Glad we got Remington,
抱歉我们没找到苏
but I'm sorry we didn't find Sue.
直觉告诉我案子比我想象的还要复杂
My nose tells me there's more to that case than I imagine.
-你会找到她的  -我会的
- You'll find her. - I will.
同时  我会忙于保护中城的安全
And in the meantime, I'll be busy keeping Central City safe.
乔  我们今天还去那个典礼吗
We still on for that ceremony today, Joe?
当然  庆典见
Oh yeah, see you there.
所以你做了吗
So did you do it?
你拥抱了新的自我吗
Did you embrace your new identity?
你见到娜塔莉了吗  你约她了吗
Did you see Natalie? Did you ask her out?
-她同意了吗  -是的  是的  没有
- Did she say yes? - Yes, yes, and no.
切斯特  我很抱歉  你还好吗
Chester, I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
其实我从未感觉更好过
I've actually never felt better.
上一次我约娜塔莉
Uh, the last time I went to ask Natalie out,
我怕的要死
I was scared as hell.
今天  我克服了那份恐惧
Today, I conquered that fear.
她说了不  但是我对自己说了好
Yo, she said no, but I said yes to me.
我为你感到开心
All right, well, I am very happy for you.
我认为
I think.
你  你在为你的公司做广告
Hey, you're-- you're marketing your firm.
这是拥抱新的自我的第一步
Yeah, yeah, it is the first step in embracing the new me.
塞西尔·霍尔顿
我想谢谢你的鼓励
You know, I wanted to thank you for your encouragement.
说到鼓励
And speaking of encouragement,
你会非常适合在尖端科研实验室
you know, you'd fit in nicely at S.T.A.R. Labs.
常联系
Don't be a stranger.
那...
That...
简直是史诗级的
would be so epic!
史诗级  史诗级
Epic. Epic.
史诗级
Epic.
给你
Here you go.
好点了吗
Better?
是的  谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
你为什么对我这么好
Why are you being so nice to me?
这么说吧  你让我想起了一个人
Let's just say you remind me of someone.
-另一个二重身  -差不多吧
- Another doppelganger. - Something like that.
做得好
Good job.
过去的五年
The last five years,
我试着保护中城的安全
I've tried to keep Central City safe.
但是随着新的威胁兴起  你们会不只需要我
But as new threats arise, you'll need more than me.
这是为什么我很自豪我发现了一位
Which is why I'm proud to recognize a hero
为了这座城市把他的生命一次又一次
who's put his life on the line for this city
置于危险之中的英雄
time and time again.
一位值得我们赞誉的英雄
A hero who deserves our recognition.
伸缩人
The Elongated Man.
如今中城有了另一个希望的标志
Now Central City has another symbol of hope.
今天在听的各位
To every woman, every man,
女士  先生和孩子
and every child listening today,
早在获得超能力之前
I have wanted to protect Central City
我就一直想保护中城
since before I ever even got my powers.
这是我的家  我很爱这里
This is my home and I love it here.
所以今天  我在此保证
And so today, I hereby promise
我会用尽我最后一口气
that I will defend Central City
来保护中城
with my dying breath.
在总结陈述前  我和
Before we wrap up, there is someone
韦斯特队长想请个人上台
that Captain West and I would like to bring up here.
现场调查员巴里·艾伦  请上台
CSI Barry Allen, please come up.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
不止有那些穿着斗篷和制服的人
Uh, those who wear capes and costumes
在保护我们的安全
aren't the only ones that keep us safe.
还有一些无名英雄
There are some unsung heroes as well,
就像这个人
like this man.
这个人靠破案为哀悼的家庭带去正义
This man has solved crimes to give mourning families justice.
他是一名从不放弃
He's a CCPD team member
任何一起案子的中城警局成员
who's never given up on a single case.
这个人拯救中城的次数比任何人都多
This man has saved Central City more times than anyone knows.
所以是时候我们感谢他
So it's time that we thank him.
是时候
It's time that...
我感谢他
that I thank him.
所以  不再赘言
So without further ado...
巴里·艾伦警官  代表中城警局
Officer Barry Allen, on behalf of CCPD,
我们授予你他们的最高荣誉
we present you with their highest honor--
荣誉勋章
the Medal of Honor.
谢谢你的付出
Thank you for your service.
荣誉勋章
很帅吧  看看它有多闪亮
Pretty cool, huh? Look how shiny it is.
拉尔夫  那很好
Yeah, that's great, Ralph.
这是你想见我的原因吗
Um, is this why you wanted to meet me?
是的
Yes.
我还想给你看这个
And I wanted to show you this.
我在迈斯特的派对上拍的
I took it at Meister's party.
我见过那个胸针
I recognize that pin.
猜猜还有谁出现在了米德韦市
Guess who else showed up in Midway City?
致命紫光
Ultraviolet?
谢谢  拉尔夫  交给公民报
Thanks Ralf, citizens is on it.
很棒的新闻发布会
Great press conference.
我有个后续问题
I have a follow up question.